DELIVERANCE TIME
At The SCOAN Live Service, Wise Man Christopher ministers God's Word and power
to the people in the name of Jesus Christ.
Under the check and conduct of the Holy Spirit,
the Wise Man is led to pray for this lady,
who begins to undergo spirit deliverance from the yoke of satan upon her life.
Let's watch what happened next.
Speak! Who are you?
Speak out!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
We are languages from the third and fourth heavens.
Pastors use us without discerning.
We rule churches Members speak. If you like, try me.
We abort babies; no one carries babies
and when we use that language, that pregnancy is gone.
When we touch your stomach, we rule; we take absolute control.
We are pledges her ancestors did not redeem. We go and come.
As for our language, it takes mighty hands to take it away.
We easily give free of charge. You cannot send us away.
You said you rule.
We rule. Yes, we rule.
How do you rule?
We give languages they do not understand.
Instead of them to use their plain words to speak to God,
they use languages that they don't understand.
When they speak, we come. We descend mightily.
She said she went for a prayer meeting.
One of the members taught her how to speak in tongues.
She didn't know it was fake.
When she is pregnant, we abort it.
You said when people speak in different languages they don't understand,
you make use of this language to destroy them.
How many of such people have you destroyed
and how do you carry out this destruction?
Oh! When you speak, you invite us. We come to the church.
Who are you people?
Spirits from the third and fourth heavens.
They dance around the kingdom of snake.
Her surname is that of a royal python.
The local one, they call it the "dabri" - royal python.
Her ancestors did not redeem that pledge - they didn't.
The men womanise. The women, when they marry, they are sent out.
She thinks she wants to run to light.
We saw her star, her star of light, shining in darkness.
We would not allow her to shine.
She sees. When she sleeps, she has thousand dreams.
No one to interpret because we didn't allow her to understand.
How do you carry out your plan of destruction of those that speak in
languages they do not understand? Explain.
When they come, pastors speak and do not understand.
They cannot discern; they are not good sheperds.
They would place their hands on your tummy and pray for safe delivery,
praying for you to carry the pregnancy safely.
When we put our hands there, we take possession of the womb.
How long have you been operating?
Long ago.
What have you done to her career?
For her career - she is a good teacher.
But when she was writing on the board the last time I visited her,
the children went out and she was going write 'homework' on the board.
She saw me laughing but didn't mind. Do you know why?
She was carrying the Anointing Sticker.
She told me there was fire around her.
What is in the Anointing Sticker from The SCOAN?
Is it not fire?
If we come with fire, you will quench it with water.
She is always sleeping under her TV with Anointing Stickers here and there.
We can't.
That is how you people have been tormenting us.
You said you can't, why?
How can we go near her?
One day, she forgot to pray and when she was sleeping, we came.
She refused to speak in tongues.
When she discovered that we were chasing her, she spoke in tongues and we replied.
Then, she refused to speak.
We forced her that night to speak.
When she spoke, we injected her leg.
We forced medicine into her throat and there's nothing here.
What have you done to her husband?
As for her husband, they handed him to us, the supreme authority.
Supreme authority, where?
Third and fourth heavens.
So, we took control.
When they take their salaries, it is nowhere to be found.
How did you enter this body?
Is it not drink and food?
Then, the ancestors. It was long ago.
We come and go.
It is only mighty and strong hands that can take her away.
Did you know that she was coming to The SCOAN where you cannot escape?
I knew you'd chain me. You seized me with chains.
How can I escape?
You demons, Jesus Christ is greater than the combined forces of hell and earth.
You have no hiding place. Now, go!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ, come out of this body!
Come back here! Come out of her!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come out of her!
Thank You, Lord.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Out!
You must!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come out of this body, you principalities!
Out! You must!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come out of this body!
This is not your temple. Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Out!
You must!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come out of her!
We will leave her womb.
You have no option than to leave.
Come out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Out!
Hallelujah. In Jesus' name.
Sister, rise up. You are delivered, in the name of Jesus Christ.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Sister, how are you?
I am fine.
What are you doing there?
I am relaxing.
You are doing what?
Relaxing.
Can you remember what happened to you?
No, I was just feeling dizzy.
You said that you are demons operating in the third and fourth heavens.
No, I am a human being.
And you use speaking in tongues to initiate and destroy people.
I went for a service where they told us to receive the fruits of the Spirit.
People were praying in tongues.
I told the leader that I had not received, so I couldn't speak.
I slept and dreamt of a certain woman in church who held a high position.
She was speaking and asked me in my dream to speak along with her.
When I woke up, I told the leader.
He told me that was it; I would speak.
When I started speaking - one night, people were chasing me
and when I spoke, they replied.
It was when I was pregnant that the pressure came to speak in tongues.
I am not a demon.
That demon that made use of your body in the past is cast out
and will never return to you.
Amen. Thank You, Jesus!
Follow Jesus. He is the One who has set you free. Follow Him.
Thank You, Jesus! I am delivered forever! Thank You, Lord!
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Mrs Bembeh Cornelia.
The man beside me is my husband.
We are from Ghana.
I want to thank God for what He has done in my life.
He delivered me and saved my life.
It all started when I was yearning to grow in the Spirit.
I was born into an orthodox church.
We were advised that if you wanted to grow in the Spirit,
you should join their charismatic group. So, I decided to join.
When we joined, they asked us to go through a 'Life In The Spirit' seminar
where we would be guided to receive the gifts of the Holy Spirit.
So, in the process, we would go on weekends.
My family was 'Dabri', which in English is 'The Royal Python'.
After I joined the charismatic group,
the night they prayed that we should receive the gifts of the Holy Spirit,
there were so many gifts mentioned.
When it was time for the gift of tongues, I couldn't receive and was sad.
I went to sleep that night and saw one of the leaders in my dream
who was speaking in tongues.
She asked me to speak as she was speaking but I couldn't.
The next day, I approached the Reverend in charge.
He asked me to speak what I heard and I did.
He said that I should take it up from there as that was it.
So, I started speaking in tongues.
The next night, I saw a big snake
and the snake spoke to me in a language I understood.
In that dream, I got scared and woke up.
Later, I saw strange women chasing me.
I decided to pray but realised that in my prayers, it was not coming out.
I tried every means to run away from them.
In my prayers, I spoke in tongues and the strange women replied to me.
I got afraid. They also spoke in tongues but I couldn't understand.
I woke up from the dream and was very scared.
Any time I went to churches and prayer meetings,
I would hear people speak the same language
the strange women spoke to me in the dream.
Any time they spoke it, I felt some movements in my tummy.
At times, I would get goose pimples on my body.
The job for the church of God now is to come together
and send out the strange people that enter church.
That is the job. If not, I don't see the church growing again.
The main job now for the church of God is to come together,
pray and send out these strange people.
Can't you hear what she is saying?
She said the next time she went into church,
she started hearing the same language those strange women spoke.
Everybody was speaking that in the same church, ignorantly.
So to flush out these people in the church, we have to pray to God, come together -
it is not what one person can do; the body must come together, fast and pray.
These strange spirits entered the church and have taken the prominent seats.
The most prominent - they are not just ordinary church members;
they are in a prominent position.
That makes it very difficult.
Can you now say that this sister is a foolish sister?
She doesn't know what she is saying?
Look at the beauty, the appearance of the person that is talking.
Look at what she is saying.
You know the last time when the issue of churches, this and that was coming in -
they said, is this church a church of God, this church is a church of God.
No, the name does not matter.
What matters is the righteousness of God.
What matters is the Bible which is our standard.
What matters is what we are doing in the assembly.
Tell your neighbour: What matters is what we are doing in the assembly.
The name of the assembly, the name of the church does not matter.
What matters is what we are doing in the assembly.
Not where you are but what you are.
You say, one is orthodox, one is this,
one is charismatic, one is pentecostal,
one is this, one is that. Those names do not matter.
What matters is what we are doing in the assembly.
After I began speaking in tongues, I realised that it was scaring me.
At night, when I went outside, I couldn't look into the sky
because I saw snakes and strange animals coming out from the sky.
Physically, I saw snakes all around me, chasing me.
People that died long ago, whom I knew, were all around me and coffins.
At times, I would hear strange voices, telling me I would die.
I saw myself being pushed into a grave or sea.
I couldn't bear it anymore. So, I was looking for my deliverance everywhere.
When I was about to get married, on the eve of my marriage,
I heard strange voices calling me.
I hesitated. So, they started shooting arrows at me.
I had to run quickly to the prayer centre and sleep there.
It was the same church that I was attending that had this charismatic group.
You are telling us now that the same church now formed a charismatic group, isn't it?
Yes, Man of God.
We want you to put more light on how they formed the charismatic group,
how you acquired this speaking in tongues,
how you received it in the dream,
and when you met the minister, how the minister encouraged you.
It was that night that they prayed for us to receive the fruit of the Holy Spirit.
I could not and I was sad
because the reverend in charge told us that one of the easiest gifts to receive
from the Holy Spirit was that of speaking in tongues.
I was sad and went to sleep.
In my dream, I saw one of the leaders.
She asked me to speak after her in the dream.
But I could not speak in the dream.
The next day, I went to the reverend and explained my encounter in the dream to him.
Ok. In that dream, you saw one of the ministers?
Yes.
And she said to you in that dream that you should speak after her
but in that dream, you could not say it?
No, I couldn't say it.
But then you woke up--
And I asked the reverend.
Physically?
Yes. He asked me to speak the way the woman did.
I did; I spoke in tongues.
He said, "That is it; begin from there, you will grow in it".
The day I spoke to him, it was just a short one.
Later on, I realised it became very lengthy.
I could not stop it; the urge kept coming.
When I was pregnant, the urge increased.
Before I knew it, I miscarried.
How did you then know that what you were doing was wrong;
speaking in tongues - the one you were saying was not from God
but from the pit of hell? How did you know?
I realised it when I was being chased by strange women in my dreams.
I was praying but the actual prayer in plain language was not coming.
Suddenly, my speaking in tongues came and it was bold.
The women in my dream replied to me in tongues.
That was when I got scared.
When I went to churches, I heard pastors and prayer warriors
praying in the same language and I got frightened.
That was when I realised that it was fake.
Since last week when I was delivered,
I don't have the urge to speak it anymore and I sleep soundly.
What are your dreams?
At times, I dream I'm in the chapel working with you or I'm somewhere teaching children.
Why should deliverance flush out that tongue?
If that tongue is from God, the deliverance should enhance it.
That means it is not from the same source.
90% of us speak what we don't understand
and what we cannot stand to say is from this place, from that place.
Ask your neighbour: Are we actually saved?
But mind you, there is true tongue from Heaven!
There is speaking in tongues from Heaven.
But how do we know?
Ask your neighbour: How do we know the one from God?
The one from God will give you comfort and peace.
If that tongue is from God, it will first of all work on you,
before you can begin to work on others.
The Bible says, you are saved to save others.
Tell your neighbour: You are saved to save others.
It is not possible for someone who is not saved to begin to save others.
You will first of all be saved before you can now save others.
Out of the abundance of the heart, the mouth speaks.
It is what you carry, what is inside here, that will speak out and give to others.
You cannot give all what is here; you just give out of it.
It is not possible to give all you have; you give out of it.
And the person will now be the one to build on it by staying steadfast in the Lord.
Are you with me?
So, I will give you out of this - out of many, I will give you.
When I give you, you now stand for God.
From there, you will begin to build on it.
So, it is not possible for someone who is speaking in tongues
now to face bitterness, pain and keep speaking in tongues.
That is to tell you - look, this one is from the pit of hell.
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ali Bimpe.
The woman standing by my side is my lovely wife.
I am here to thank God for what He has done in our lives by delivering my wife
and also to confirm that all she said is true.
We got married about three and a half years ago and there the problem started.
We never slept in our room in the night.
She was always seeing things in the air.
Anytime she slept, she always woke up, complaining of a terrible dream,
seeing dead people.
You mean, when you were together in the house, she spoke this language?
Yes, she did sometimes.
She had been seeing dead people in her dreams.
Sometimes, she saw people drawing her into a water or a grave.
She saw other smaller demons.
Thank you very much. I want to meet the family, I want to be part of your family.
So, thank you very much.
There is tongue, speaking in tongues.
But there is fake one.
How will you know when you don't know what you are saying?
If I'm talking when I don't know that God is the one that is talking through me,
how will I know that it is not from satan then?
It is when I know that what I'm saying is from God,
that is when I can also believe that it will do what I asked it to do.
But when I say something and I don't know that what I'm saying is from God,
definitely, any creature can have access to it.
If I'm talking to you?
It can be manipulated.
When you say something, "cha cha cha", this "cha cha cha", where is it from?
Is this "cha cha cha" from God?